Guide to the Nina Rosenblum Papers MSS.558
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series XVI. Zahira's Peace, 2004-2014; 4.48 Linear Feet in 1 manuscript box, 3 record cartons, and 1 cassette box; 11 Betacam_SP; 11 Digital_Betacam; 1 MiniDV; 5 VHS; 1.26 Gigabytes in 55 computer files
  - Subseries XVI.D. Production Materials, 4.48 Linear Feet in 1 manuscript box, 3 record cartons, and 1 cassette box; 7 Betacam_SP; 11 Digital_Betacam; 1 MiniDV; 5 VHS; 1.24 Gigabytes in 37 computer files
    This subseries contains materials related to the production of the film. Most of the materials consist of video recordings in Spanish and English, but there are also digital photographs and daily planners.
    - Daily Planners, 2004-2005 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Electronic Recordings and Photographs, 2005-2010; FA_MSS_558_ER_75
    - English Versions
      - English Version, August 23, 2004 (Box 23, Vhs 558.0290)
      - English Version, September 20, 2004 (Box 23, Betacam sp 558.0302)
      - English Version, December 24, 2004 (Box 23, Digital betacam 558.0297)
      - English Version, January 22, 2005 (Box 32, Vhs 558.0334)
      - Zahira's Peace, August 21, 2004 (Box 29, Betacam sp 558.0547)
      - Zahira's Peace, February 5, 2005 (Box 29, Betacam sp 558.0546)
      - Zahira's Peace, February 5, 2005 (Box 23, Betacam sp 558.0296)
      - Zahira's Peace, February 26, 2005 (Box 29, Digital betacam 558.0555)
    - Imagine #1-2, undated (Box 44, Minidv 558.0465)
    - Imagine #3 -- Original Master, April 14, 2004 (Box 23, Digital betacam 558.0299)
    - New York Women in Film and Television Version, September 29, 2004 (Box 23, Digital betacam 558.0300)
    - Spanish Versions
      - Compactado Zahira 1, April 2, 2004 (Box 29, Digital betacam 558.0556)
      - Compactado Zahira 2, April 2, 2004 (Box 29, Digital betacam 558.0549)
      - No Subtitles, February 26, 2005; FA_MSS_558_ER_111
      - No Subtitles; With Labels, February 26, 2005 (Box 23, Digital betacam 558.0293)
      - Repicado Trailer, March 4, 2005 (Box 23, Betacam sp 558.0298)
      - Version Limpid (Final Version), February 24, 2005 (Box 23, Digital betacam 558.0294)
      - Zahira: La Que Florece, August 21, 2004 (Box 23, Vhs 558.0291)
      - Zahira: La Que Florece, August 24, 2004 (Box 23, Vhs 558.0289)
      - Zahira: La Que Florece, undated (Box 23, Digital betacam 558.0301)
    - Subtitled Versions
      - Spanish Subtitles, February 26, 2005 (Box 23, Betacam sp 558.0295)
      - Spanish with Subtitles, December 28, 2004; FA_MSS_558_ER_110
      - Subtitles, April 8, 2005 (Box 23, Vhs 558.0292)
    - Tape 3, April 2, 2004 (Box 29, Digital betacam 558.0551)
    - Tape 4, April 2, 2004 (Box 29, Digital betacam 558.0550)
    - Trailer, undated (Box 23, Betacam sp 558.0304)
  - Subseries XVI.E. Screenings and Festivals, 2005-2007; .44 Linear Feet in 1 manuscript box; 72 kilobytes in 3 computer files
    This subseries includes materials related to the screening of the film and participation in film festivals. Materials include festival programs, schedules, and correspondence.
    - Invitation, Announcement, and Speech, 2005-2006; FA_MSS_558_ER_76
    - Schedules, Correspondence, and Programs, 2005-2007 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Series XVII. Twin Lenses, 1998-2013; 6.67 Linear Feet in 6 manuscript boxes, 1 cassette box, and 3 record cartons; 12 audiocassette; 24 Betacam_SP; 13 Digital_Betacam; 22 VHS; 32.08 Gigabytes in 36 computer files
  This series consists of materials related to Twin Lenses, a feature documentary highlighting the careers of fashion photographers and twin sisters Frances McLaughlin Gill and Kathryn Abbe, both of whom worked in New York City during the 1940s-1950s. Materials related to the production, marketing, and screening of the film contain a scrapbook, press, photographs by the subjects, posters, and film elements (such as stills, master copies, interviews, and a final demo shoot) on various media.
  - Subseries XVII.A. Administrative Materials, 2007-2013; 182 kilobytes in 7 computer files
    This subseries includes office files such as correspondence and manuscript drafts for either a related book or exhibition catalogue.
    - Book/Exhibition Catalogue, 2009-2013; FA_MSS_558_ER_77
    - Correspondence, 2007-2013; FA_MSS_558_ER_78
  - Subseries XVII.B. Marketing Materials, 2008-2010; .44 Linear Feet in 1 manuscript box; 14.1 Megabytes in 10 computer files
    This subseries includes materials used in the marketing of the film such as posters, synopses, and photographs.
    - Electronic Records -- Poster, DVD Cover, and Press Release, 2008-2010; FA_MSS_558_ER_79
    - Synopses, Postcards, and Photographs, 2008 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Subseries XVII.C. Press and Reviews, 2008-2013; .44 Linear Feet in 1 manuscript box; 1.23 Megabytes in 2 computer files
    This subseries consists of publicity materials related to the film including reviews and clippings.
    - Clippings and Articles, 2008-2009 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Electronic Records -- Articles, 2010-2013; FA_MSS_558_ER_80
  - Subseries XVII.D. Production Materials, 1998-2013; 6.23 Linear Feet in 5 manuscript boxes, 3 record cartons, and 1 cassette box; 12 audiocassette; 24 Betacam_SP; 13 Digital_Betacam; 22 VHS; 32 Gigabytes in 12 computer files
    This subseries contains materials related to the production of the film, most of which are audio and video recordings.
    - Audio Recordings
      - #5-6, undated (Box 62, Audiocassette 558.0017)
      - #7-8, undated (Box 62, Audiocassette 558.0018)
      - #10, undated (Box 62, Audiocassette 558.0009)
      - #11-12, undated (Box 62, Audiocassette 558.0013)
      - #13-14, undated (Box 62, Audiocassette 558.0014)
      - #15-16, undated (Box 62, Audiocassette 558.0012)
      - Abbe -- Tape 1, undated (Box 62, Audiocassette 558.0019)
      - Abbe -- Tape 2, undated (Box 62, Audiocassette 558.0011)
      - Abbe -- Tape 3, undated (Box 62, Audiocassette 558.0010)
      - Abbe -- Tape 4, undated (Box 62, Audiocassette 558.0015)
      - Abbe -- Tape 5, undated (Box 62, Audiocassette 558.0016)
      - Jimmy Abbe Memorial, undated (Box 62, Audiocassette 558.0520)
    - Electronic Recordings, 2008-2013; FA_MSS_558_ER_81
    - Master Video Recordings
      - #5A, December 13, 1998 (Box 58, Betacam sp 558.0265)
      - #6, December 13, 1998 (Box 58, Betacam sp 558.0264)
      - #7, December 13, 1998 (Box 58, Betacam sp 558.0263)
      - #8, December 13, 1998 (Box 58, Betacam sp 558.0262)
      - #9, December 13, 1998 (Box 58, Betacam sp 558.0261)
      - #10 -- Interview, December 13, 1998 (Box 58, Betacam sp 558.0260)
      - #11 -- Tom and Kathryn, December 14, 1998 (Box 59, Betacam sp 558.0672)
      - #12, December 14, 1998 (Box 59, Betacam sp 558.0675)
      - #13, December 14, 1998 (Box 59, Betacam sp 558.0673)
      - #14, December 14, 1998 (Box 59, Betacam sp 558.0674)
      - #15, December 14, 1998 (Box 59, Betacam sp 558.0671)
      - Abbe 1, undated (Box 59, Digital betacam 558.0679)
      - Abbe 3, undated (Box 59, Digital betacam 558.0677)
      - Twin Lenses -- Master, undated (Box 59, Betacam sp 558.0680)
    - Stills
      - Abbe -- Tape 1, January 15, 2000 (Box 45, Vhs 558.0650)
      - Abbe -- Tape 1, January 15, 2000 (Box 57, Betacam sp 558.0668)
      - Abbe -- Tape 1 -- Master, January 15, 2000 (Box 57, Digital betacam 558.0661)
      - Abbe -- Tape 2, January 15, 2000 (Box 57, Betacam sp 558.0667)
      - Abbe -- Tape 2, January 15, 2000 (Box 45, Vhs 558.0648)
      - Abbe -- Tape 2 -- Master, January 15, 2000 (Box 57, Digital betacam 558.0660)
      - Abbe -- Tape 3, January 15, 2000 (Box 45, Vhs 558.0647)
      - Abbe -- Tape 3, January 15, 2000 (Box 57, Betacam sp 558.0666)
      - Abbe -- Tape 3 -- Master, January 15, 2000 (Box 57, Digital betacam 558.0659)
      - Abbe -- Tape 4, January 15, 2000 (Box 57, Betacam sp 558.0665)
      - Abbe -- Tape 4, January 15, 2000 (Box 45, Vhs 558.0646)
      - Abbe -- Tape 4 -- Master, January 15, 2000 (Box 57, Digital betacam 558.0658)
      - Abbe -- Tape 5, January 15, 2000 (Box 57, Betacam sp 558.0664)
      - Abbe -- Tape 5 -- Master, January 15, 2000 (Box 57, Digital betacam 558.0657)
      - Abbe -- Tape 6, January 15, 2000 (Box 57, Betacam sp 558.0663)
      - Abbe -- Tape 6, January 15, 2000 (Box 46, Vhs 558.0283)
      - Tape 6 -- Master, January 15, 2000 (Box 58, Digital betacam 558.0271)
      - Tape 7 -- Master -- Final Demo Shoot, January 15, 2000 (Box 57, Digital betacam 558.0662)
    - Video Recordings
      - #1, undated (Box 58, Betacam sp 558.0270)
      - #2, undated (Box 58, Betacam sp 558.0269)
      - #3, undated (Box 58, Betacam sp 558.0268)
      - #4, undated (Box 58, Betacam sp 558.0267)
      - #5, undated (Box 58, Betacam sp 558.0266)
      - #16, undated (Box 59, Betacam sp 558.0670)
      - Abbe, undated (Box 59, Digital betacam 558.0678)
      - Abbe #2, undated (Box 59, Digital betacam 558.0676)
      - Abbe #4 -- Jimmy and Kathryn and Their Careers, undated (Box 46, Vhs 558.0279)
      - Abbe #5 -- Jimmy and Kathryn and Their Careers, undated (Box 46, Vhs 558.0282)
      - Abbe #6, undated (Box 46, Vhs 558.0278)
      - Abbe #10, undated (Box 46, Vhs 558.0277)
      - Abbe -- Tape 1 -- Dub of 1-4, September 9, 1999 (Box 46, Vhs 558.0273)
      - Abbe -- Tape 2 -- Dub of 5-10, undated (Box 46, Vhs 558.0274)
      - Abbe -- Tape 3 -- Dub of 12-16, undated (Box 46, Vhs 558.0275)
      - In Window, undated (Box 45, Vhs 558.0655)
      - K and James #9, undated (Box 46, Vhs 558.0276)
      - Kathryn Photographs Devon, undated (Box 45, Vhs 558.0654)
      - Kathryn Abbe Talks about Her and Franny -- Tape 3, undated (Box 45, Vhs 558.0649)
      - Tape 1, undated (Box 45, Vhs 558.0645)
      - Tape 1, undated (Box 45, Vhs 558.0652)
      - Twin Lenses, August 8, 2000 (Box 28, Vhs 558.0579)
      - Twin Lenses, undated (Box 31, Digital betacam 558.0615)
      - Twin Lenses, undated (Box 31, Digital betacam 558.0616)
      - Twin Lenses, undated (Box 24, Vhs 558.0558)
      - Twin Lenses, undated (Box 28, Vhs 558.0580)
      - Twin Lenses, undated (Box 59, Vhs 558.0669)
  - Subseries XVII.E. Screenings and Festivals, 2007-2009; .44 Linear Feet in 1 manuscript box; 221 kilobytes in 5 computer files
    This subseries includes materials related to the screening of the film and participation in film festivals; materials consist of festival programs, schedules, and correspondence.
    - Announcements and Speech, 2008-2009; FA_MSS_558_ER_82
    - Schedules, Correspondence, and Programs, 2007-2008 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Series XVIII. In the Name of Democracy, 2006-2014; 4.89 Linear Feet in 2 manuscript boxes, 2 cassette boxes, 2 record cartons, and 1 small flat box; 1 audiocassette; 2 Digital_Betacam; 55 MiniDV; 115.85 Gigabytes in 678 computer files
  This series consists of materials related to In the Name of Democracy, a 2009 feature documentary about the case of Lt. Ehren Watada, the first officer in the US Army to refuse to deploy to Iraq, which resulted in a mistrial and a dishonorable discharge. Materials related to the production, marketing, and screening of the film include a scrapbook, production binder, photographs, posters, and film elements (such as interviews, audio recordings of music used, and exterior shots) on various media.
  - Subseries XVIII.A. Administrative Materials, 2007-2013; .44 Linear Feet in 1 manuscript box; 59.8 kilobytes in 4 computer files
    This subseries contains office files such as correspondence and a budget.
    - Budget, 2007 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence
      - Letters and Email Printouts, 2007-2009 (Box 14, Folder 12)
      - Electronic Records, 2008-2013; FA_MSS_558_ER_83
  - Subseries XVIII.B. Marketing Materials, 2008-2014; .44 Linear Feet in 1 manuscript box; 9.72 Megabytes in 11 computer files
    This subseries consists of materials related to the marketing of the film, such as press releases, synopses, and postcards.
    - Electronic Records -- Posters, DVD Cover, Talking Points, and Blurbs, 2009-2014; FA_MSS_558_ER_84
    - Synopses, Postcards, and Press Releases, 2008-2009 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Subseries XVIII.C. Production Materials, 2004-2012; 4.46 Linear Feet in 1 manuscript box, 2 record cartons, 1 small flat box, and 2 cassette boxes; 1 audiocassette; 2 Digital_Betacam; 54 MiniDV; 114.54 Gigabytes in 660 computer files
    This subseries contains materials related to the production of the film. Most of the materials are audio and video recordings but there are also photographs, analog tape logs, and a music list.
    - #1, undated (Box 36, Minidv 558.0396)
    - Audio Recordings
      - Anne Jackson and Eli Wallach, January 2007 (Box 62, Audiocassette 558.0233)
      - Music, 2008-2010; FA_MSS_558_ER_106
    - CWW Tapes -- B.I.T.C.
      - Part 1 of 2, August 2, 2007 (Box 36, Minidv 558.0427)
      - Part 2 of 2, August 2, 2007 (Box 36, Minidv 558.0428)
    - Eddie
      - 1 of 2, September 17, 2007 (Box 36, Minidv 558.0410)
      - Painting on Rivington St. -- 2 of 2, undated (Box 36, Minidv 558.0395)
    - Electronic Recordings, 2004-2012; FA_MSS_558_ER_85
      Some videos and photographs contain graphic images of human rights violations.
    - End Replacement -- Army Woman, undated (Box 36, Minidv 558.0440)
    - Gen. Wesley Clark, undated (Box 36, Minidv 558.0432)
    - Hartford
      - 008, April 5, 2007 (Box 36, Minidv 558.0379)
      - 009, April 5, 2007 (Box 36, Minidv 558.0380)
    - "Haru", undated (Box 36, Minidv 558.0411)
    - In the Name of Democracy, November 16, 2009 (Box 29, Digital betacam 558.0548)
    - In the Name of Democracy, June 3, 2010 (Box 30, Digital betacam 558.0541)
    - IND
      - 005 -- Fallujah, undated (Box 36, Minidv 558.0376)
      - 006 -- The War Tribunal, undated (Box 36, Minidv 558.0377)
      - 007 -- Soldiers and Students, undated (Box 36, Minidv 558.0378)
      - 010 -- Time Square Protest -- DW -- Newspaper Clips, March 14, 2006 (Box 36, Minidv 558.0381)
      - 012, undated (Box 36, Minidv 558.0386)
      - 017 -- Uncovered Iraq, undated (Box 36, Minidv 558.0439)
      - 018, undated (Box 36, Minidv 558.0391)
      - 019, undated (Box 36, Minidv 558.0392)
      - 020, undated (Box 36, Minidv 558.0393)
      - 026 -- Car Mechanic Interview -- CT, August 2007 (Box 36, Minidv 558.0401)
      - 027 -- NR -- Salisbury, CT, undated (Box 36, Minidv 558.0402)
      - 028 -- Dennis VO, undated (Box 36, Minidv 558.0403)
      - 029 -- Clark from Olbaman, undated (Box 36, Minidv 558.0404)
      - 1, March 7, 2007 (Box 36, Minidv 558.0407)
      - 3 -- Brendan and Jeremy, 2006-2007 (Box 36, Minidv 558.0406)
      - 4 -- Brendan and Jeremy, March 7, 2007 (Box 36, Minidv 558.0412)
      - 5, March 7, 2007 (Box 36, Minidv 558.0413)
      - 6, March 7, 2007 (Box 36, Minidv 558.0414)
      - "Dem", March 19, 2008 (Box 36, Minidv 558.0437)
      - "MARC 5", August 12, 2007 (Box 36, Minidv 558.0429)
    - The Leader
      - 001 -- Tape 1 of 2, undated (Box 36, Minidv 558.0372)
      - 002 -- Tape 2 of 2, undated (Box 36, Minidv 558.0373)
    - Mrs. Clark Meeting
      - 1 of 2, September 30, 2007 (Box 36, Minidv 558.0436)
      - 2 of 2, September 30, 2007 (Box 36, Minidv 558.0383)
    - "Nina's Shoot", 2008; FA_MSS_558_ER_119
    - Output NiNi, undated (Box 36, Minidv 558.0397)
    - Photographs, 2006-2010; FA_MSS_558_ER_86
    - Political Cartoonist, undated (Box 36, Minidv 558.0408)
    - Protest for War Book, February 29, 2008 (Box 36, Minidv 558.0434)
    - Research Material, 2009; FA_MSS_558_ER_89
    - Scott Stringer -- Nina Shot, March 19, 2008 (Box 40, Minidv 558.0239)
    - Tape Logs
      - Electronic Records, 2007-2012; FA_MSS_558_ER_87
      - Printed Logs, 2008-2009 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Transcript, Shot Lists, Music List, and Credits, 2007-2010; FA_MSS_558_ER_88
    - TV -- Nina
      - 022, undated (Box 36, Minidv 558.0398)
      - 023, undated (Box 36, Minidv 558.0399)
      - Video Recording, undated (Box 36, Minidv 558.0394)
    - Watada
      - #1, April 16, 2007 (Box 36, Minidv 558.0415)
      - #2, April 16, 2007 (Box 36, Minidv 558.0416)
      - #3, April 17, 2007 (Box 36, Minidv 558.0417)
      - #4, April 17, 2007 (Box 36, Minidv 558.0418)
      - #6, April 18, 2007 (Box 36, Minidv 558.0420)
      - #1 -- Watada and Haskell, April 16, 2007 (Box 36, Minidv 558.0421)
      - #2 -- Watada and Haskell, April 16, 2007 (Box 36, Minidv 558.0422)
      - #3 -- Watada and Haskell, April 17, 2007 (Box 36, Minidv 558.0423)
      - #4 -- Watada and Haskell, April 17, 2007 (Box 36, Minidv 558.0424)
      - #5 -- Watada and Haskell, April 18, 2007 (Box 36, Minidv 558.0425)
      - #6 -- Watada and Haskell, April 18, 2007 (Box 36, Minidv 558.0426)
      - #5 -- Watada, Rita, Amy, Tonya, April 18, 2007 (Box 36, Minidv 558.0419)
  - Subseries XVIII.D. Screenings, Festivals, and Press, 2009-2010; 1.23 Linear Feet in 1 manuscript box and 1 cassette box; 1 MiniDV; 3.37 Megabytes in 3 computer files
    This subseries contains publicity materials and materials related to the film screening and film festival participation. These materials include festival programs, schedules, and reviews.
    - Electronic Records -- Flyers and Schedule, 2009-2010; FA_MSS_558_ER_90
    - Festival and Screening Programs and Schedules, 2009-2010 (Box 15, Folder 1-2)
    - KJCC -- Screening and Musicians, February 24, 2010 (Box 36, Minidv 558.0384)
    - Reviews and Articles, 2009-2010 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Series XIX. Ordinary Miracles: The Photo League's New York, 1942-2014; 13.13 Linear Feet in 6 manuscript boxes, 6 record cartons, 1 medium flat box, 3 cassette boxes, 1 card box, 3 small flat boxes, and 1 flat file folder; 22 Quarter_Inch_Audio_Reel; 7 VHS; 11 16mm_film_reels; 8 audiocassette; 10 DAT; 5 Digital_Betacam; 15 DVCAM; 33 MiniDV; 7 Betacam_SP; 33.68 Gigabytes in 755 computer files
  This series encompasses materials related to Ordinary Miracles: The Photo League's New York, a 2012 feature documentary chronicling the rise and fall of the Photo League (19361951), a cooperative of photographers in New York. Materials consist of extensive research documents, such as press on member photographers, photocopied archival documents about classes and events, audio from a symposium with Walter Rosenblum and others, and news reels. Additional materials related to the production, marketing, and screening of the film include a production binder, grant application, correspondence with Photo League members, budgets, slides, negatives, contact sheets, photographs, posters, ads for the film premiere, and film elements (such as sound rolls, voiceovers, interviews, camera rolls, and trailers) on various media. Also included are photographs from a 1999 reunion of Photo League members.
  Arranged alphabetically into six subseries and alphanumerically within each one.
  - Subseries XIX.A. Administrative Materials, 1988-2011; .44 Linear Feet in 1 manuscript box
    This subseries includes office files, such as budgets, correspondence, and grant proposals.
    - Budgets, 1989-2011 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1988-2011 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Grant Proposals, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 6-7)
  - Subseries XIX.B. Marketing Materials, 2011-2014; .45 Linear Feet in 1 manuscript box and 1 oversized flat file folder; 470 Megabytes in 7 computer files
    This subseries consists of materials related to the marketing of the film, such as synopses, posters, and postcards.
    - Electronic Records -- Brochure, Posters, and DVD Cover, 2011-2014; FA_MSS_558_ER_66
    - Poster, 2012 (Flat-file-folder 2)
    - Synopses and Postcards, 2012-2013 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Subseries XIX.C. Press and Reviews, 2011-2012; .44 Linear Feet in 1 manuscript box; 39.8 Megabytes in 19 computer files
    This subseries consists of publicity materials related to the film, such as reviews and articles.
    - Articles and Clippings, 2011-2012 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Electronic Records -- Articles and Photographs, 2012; FA_MSS_558_ER_67
  - Subseries XIX.D. Production Materials, 1989-2012; 11.52 Linear Feet in 3 manuscript boxes, 6 record cartons, 3 cassette boxes, 1 card box, 2 small flat boxes, and 1 medium flat box; 16 Quarter_Inch_Audio_Reel; 2 VHS; 11 16mm_film_reels; 8 audiocassette; 10 DAT; 5 Digital_Betacam; 15 DVCAM; 33 MiniDV; 7 Betacam_SP; 29.96 Gigabytes in 73 computer files
    This subseries contains materials related to the production of the film, such as audio and video recordings. Also included are photographs and interviews from the 1999 reunion of Photo League members. Materials also consist of scripts, treatments, and tape logs.
    - Audio Recordings
      - Helen Levitt
        - Tape 2, undated (Box 33, Quarter inch audio reel 558.0480)
        - Tape 3, undated (Box 33, Quarter inch audio reel 558.0479)
      - Huberland, 1996 (Box 62, Audiocassette 558.0055)
      - Interviews with Photo League Members, 1996; FA_MSS_558_ER_107
      - Interviews with Photo League Members and New York Public Library, 1999-2010; FA_MSS_558_ER_124
      - Joe Schwartz and Jerry Liebling
        - Jerry Liebling -- Voiceover and Schwartz, undated (Box 42, Quarter inch audio reel 558.0523)
        - Joe Schwartz -- Tape 10 -- With and Without Camera, October 4, 1999 (Box 42, Quarter inch audio reel 558.0518)
        - Joe Schwartz -- Tape 11, circa 1999 (Box 33, Quarter inch audio reel 558.0476)
        - Joe Schwartz -- Tape 12, October 4, 1999 (Box 33, Quarter inch audio reel 558.0475)
      - N1, October 2, 1999 (Box 42, Quarter inch audio reel 558.0525)
      - N2, October 2, 1999 (Box 42, Quarter inch audio reel 558.0508)
      - N3, October 2, 1999 (Box 33, Quarter inch audio reel 558.0481)
      - N4, October 2, 1999 (Box 42, Quarter inch audio reel 558.0516)
      - N5, October 2, 1999 (Box 42, Quarter inch audio reel 558.0526)
      - N6, October 2, 1999 (Box 42, Quarter inch audio reel 558.0512)
      - Rebecca Lepkoff
        - Voiceover -- Tape 7, October 4, 1999 (Box 42, Quarter inch audio reel 558.0519)
        - Voiceover -- Tape 8, October 4, 1999 (Box 42, Quarter inch audio reel 558.0524)
        - Audio Recording, undated (Box 37, Dat 558.0058)
      - Sol Libsohm, June 25, 1999 (Box 37, Dat 558.0056)
      - Tape #1, undated (Box 33, Quarter inch audio reel 558.0477)
      - Tape #13, undated (Box 42, Quarter inch audio reel 558.0514)
      - Walter, undated (Box 37, Dat 558.0057)
    - Electronic Recordings, 2004-2012; FA_MSS_558_ER_68
    - Film and Video Recordings
      - #3, undated (Box 40, Minidv 558.0096)
      - #3B, October 15, 1999 (Box 22, Dvcam 558.0563)
      - #4, September 26, 2000 (Box 22, Dvcam 558.0316)
      - #5, October 15, 1999 (Box 22, Dvcam 558.0561)
      - Corbis 1, February 10, 2004 (Box 40, Minidv 558.0069)
      - Farm -- Bin 1, Shot 6 -- Archival Footage, August 24, 2011 (Box 25, Digital betacam 558.0105)
      - G. Gilbert, December 3, 2000 (Box 40, Minidv 558.0093)
      - Ida Wyman at Soho Triad Gallery, January 12, 2000 (Box 40, Minidv 558.0092)
      - Joe and Jerry in Union Square -- #4B, October 15, 1999 (Box 22, Dvcam 558.0562)
      - Joe Schwartz -- Voiceover, October 24, 1994 (Box 28, Betacam sp 558.0606)
      - Lewis Cole
        - Video Recording, December 7, 2000 (Box 40, Minidv 558.0094)
        - Video Recording, undated (Box 40, Minidv 558.0095)
        - Video Recording, undated (Box 60, Vhs 558.0204)
      - Lisa Davis
        - #2, undated (Box 40, Minidv 558.0083)
        - At Home and Peter -- 1 of 2, January 10, 2011 (Box 40, Minidv 558.0079)
        - At Home and Peter -- 2 of 2, January 10, 2011 (Box 40, Minidv 558.0066)
      - Naomi Rosenblum
        - Mason Visits Mom, 2010 (Box 40, Minidv 558.0082)
        - Mom, January 31, 2008 (Box 40, Minidv 558.0078)
        - Naomi -- Social Photography, undated (Box 39, Minidv 558.0074)
      - New York Public Library
        - NYPL Photo League 1 -- Digital Master, undated (Box 22, Minidv 558.0045)